

- GHAZIABAD, INDIA, 201003
- 8707071151
- ✓ SHIVENDRAMISHRA281292@ GMAIL.COM

# SUMMARY

Sales professional with 9+ year experience in lead generation and Channel sales, FMCG, B2B And B2C sales. Seeking a good work perspective in a company which offers a congenial, invigorating & challenging work atmosphere with long carrier growth prospects. To be build up a bright future and a challenging and growth oriented position in a progressive company, where I contribute to the organization's success with my sales expertise & through my innovative ideas and desire to achieve excellence.

#### SKILLS

- Market surveys and research
- Sales strategies
- Market data analysis
- Sales pitches
- Ability to work under pressure
- Microsoft Excel
- Google sheet

# ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

- Father Name-Dr Dinesh Mishra
- Gender-Male
- DOB-28<sup>th</sup> Dec 1992
- Nationality-Indian
- Marital Status-Married

# SHIVENDRA MISHRA

#### **EXPERIENCE**

#### October 2021 - Current

Territory Sales Manager 1K KIRANA BAZAR | GHAZIABAD, INDIA

- ➤ Handling 40-50 Retail outlets and On-trade sections for the company in Ghaziabad.
- > Onboard new retail outlet and expanding the territory.
- Sales executives and BTLs team handling.
- Management of inventories and stock of all retails outlets including. keeping detailed records of inventory usage and sales.
- Advising management on Responsible for delivery of a monthly sale revenue targets of assign stores in the territory.
- Ensure payment collection from every store on timely.
- > Handling wholesale and institutional sale.
- Planning of promotional events for retail outlet in the form of lucky draw, drawing competition, play and win competition etc to increase The sales of stores.
- Providing encouragement to team members, including communicating team goals and identifying.
- Conducts team meetings to update members on best practices and continuing expectations.
- ➤ Generating and shares comprehensive and detailed reports about team performance, mission related objectives and deadlines.
- Ensure company brand materials and physical working stock ordering necessary for all retail outlets. space meet and exceed company presentation standards.
- Providing quality customer service, including interacting with
- customers, answering customer enquiries & effectively handling customer complaints.
- > Supporting Retailer to performs management's duties and work on key points of retail.

#### February 2021 - September 2021

SR.SALES EXECUTIVE KULDEEP OSWAL HOSIERY MILLS PVT LTD | LUCKNOW, INDIA

- > Bring new channel partners on board and maintain relationships with Existing channel partners.
- > Understand customer and business needs to cross-sell and up-sell the company's products.
- Coordinate with other company personnel such as the support team and management team to deliver and meet customer/ partner expectations.
- > Act as a bridge for communication between the customers/partners and the team.
- Access, clarify and validate partner needs and performances at regular intervals and maintain a high partner satisfaction rate with the company.
- Coordinate with other sales channels to avoid any potential conflicts.

# **April 2019 - February 2021**

SR STORE EXECUTIVE DEE VEE ASSOCIATES - FRENCHISEE OF GODREJ INTERIO | LUCKNOW, INDIA

#### **October 2016 - March 2019**

Sales Executive AKRITI CREATION-DEALER OF GODREJ INTERIO | LUCKNOW, INDIA

# **April 2014 - October 2016**

Customer Relationship Executive RKBK LTD | LUCKNOW, INDIA

# **EDUCATION**

2014

**Master of Business Administration (MBA)** | MARKETING AND FINANCE AKS MANAGMENT COLLAGE, LUCKNOW, Lucknow, UP

2012

**BECHLOR OF ART | HISTORY** 

RML AWADH UNIVERSITY, Faizabad, UP

# **LANGUAGES**

Hindi: First Language

English: